<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on VORONOI</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on VORONOI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 12:17:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/blog/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 12:17:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/publications/</guid>
      <description>BibTeX format @Misc{voronoi-web-page, Author = &amp;quot;Daniel R. Livingston, Carl W. Gable, Satish Karra, Manuel Sentis, Michael J. Hannon, Rajesh Pawar&amp;quot;, Title = &amp;quot;{VORONOI} {W}eb page&amp;quot;, Note = &amp;quot;http://www.github.com/lanl/voronoi&amp;quot;, Year = &amp;quot;2018&amp;quot; }  Publications   Hannon, M. et al. Permeability Estimates of Fractured Cylindrical Samples by the Analysis of Pressure Transients. Proceedings of the TOUGH Symposium 2018, Berkeley, CA, Oct 8-10, 2018
 Livingston, D. et al. VORONOI: An Orthogonally-Constrained and Numerically Accurate Processor for Subsurface Codes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 17:26:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information For bug reports and feature requests, submit a ticket at GitHub Issues.
For everything else, contact Daniel Livingston at livingston@lanl.gov
Development Team  Daniel Livingston, Los Alamos National Laboratory Carl Gable, Los Alamos National Laboratory Satish Karra, Los Alamos National Laboratory Manuel Sentis, Swiss Federal Safety Inspectorate Michael Hannon, Jr., Indiana Geological &amp;amp; Water Survey Rajesh Pawar, Los Alamos National Laboratory  Related Web Pages  VORONOI GitHub LaGriT Mesh Generation Toolkit Meshing for Geological Applications (Los Alamos National Laboratory) Computational Earth Science (EES-16) at Los Alamos National Laboratory FEHM PFLOTRAN TOUGH</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>